With Amazon Buy Shipping, you can access Amazon's negotiated shipping rates or link your own rates
from your FedEx or UPS account for seller-fulfilled prime or non-prime orders.
Before linking a carrier account, there are two steps you need to take.
First, review the terms and conditions in the Buy Shipping Services Terms and Conditions Help page.
Second, update your contact information in the Buy Shipping Preferences.
Go to Settings, click Account Info, click Shipping and Returns Information, then Buy Shipping Preferences.
Under Manage Your Ship From Locations, click Edit and review or update your email address and phone
number.
To begin linking your carrier accounts, go to Buy Shipping Preferences in Seller Central and click
Manage Your Carrier Accounts.
Then click Link Account.
Choose either the FedEx or UPS tile to start the process.
For FedEx accounts, you'll need to provide your 9-digit account number, contact information including
name and address, your FedEx email address and your company name.
For UPS accounts, you'll need your UPS account number, the account zip code from your original UPS
registration and your current shipping location information.
After entering your information, you'll authenticate your account.
For FedEx, you'll receive a one-time password by email or phone.
For UPS, you'll sign in through the UPS website using your UPS.
com credentials.
Once authentication is complete, your account status will show as active.
It's important to note that your shipping rates should appear within 3-5 business days after linking
your account.
If you linked your FedEx account before May 2025 or your UPS account uses Access Key-Based Authorization,
you'll need to re-authenticate your accounts in Seller Central.
Without re-authentication, you'll only see Amazon's pre-negotiated rates instead of your own.
To re-authenticate your accounts, go to Manage Your Carrier Accounts and select Authenticate next
to your FedEx or UPS account and enter your account information.
For FedEx, choose to receive a one-time password by email or phone and enter the password to complete
authentication.
For UPS, sign in through the UPS website using your UPS.
com credentials and follow the prompts to complete the process.
Each UPS account must be re-authenticated individually.
The Merchant Fulfillment API is another way for you to purchase shipping through Buy Shipping without
the need to log in to your Seller account in Seller Central.
You'll need to review and agree to the terms and conditions for each carrier service you plan to
use.
After reviewing, select the "I agree" checkbox for each carrier, then select Submit.
If you experience any issues during the linking or authentication process, such as frozen pages
or validation errors, visit the Manage Your Carrier Accounts and the Buy Shipping Preferences Help
pages.